- Hello ? - It 's me .
Oh , am I bothering you , Francesco ?
Oh , don 't worry .
Had to get out of the shower sometime .
Hold on a minute , Franco .
You were saying , Franco ?
No , nothing ,
just calling to see how you 're doing .
Mmm .
You know how things are .
Life goes on !
Gnaghi !
Nyah ?
I 've been shouting at you for hours !
Gnaghi !
He 's Chigini , the surveyor .
12th row , third grave , right ?
Nyah !
Grave three .
Here we go .
I know you 've heard this before ,
but this time , my dear Chigini , it is forever !
Rest in peace .
Oh , my back !
What a waste of good marble !
Never looks right when you fix it .
All this fancy packaging .
I don 't know why they don 't just cover the graves with dirt !
Nyah .
The gun !
I forgot the fucking gun !
Eat !
Gnaghi !
Give me the spade !
Gnaghi , give me the fucking spade !
Eat !
There we go .
You handle the rest , Gnaghi .
My name is Francesco Dellamorte .
Weird name , isn 't it ?
Francis of Death .
Saint Francis of Death .
I 've often thought of having it changed .
Andre Dellamorte would be nicer , for example .
I 'm the watchman of the Buffalora cemetery .
I don 't know how the epidemic started .
All I know is that some people ,
on the seventh night after their death ,
come back to life .
I call them Returners ,
but , frankly , I can 't understand
why they 're so anxious to return .
The only way to get rid of them once
and for all is to split their heads open .
A spade will do it , but a Dum-Dum bullet is best .
Come and have a glass of wine .
Nyah !
Is this the beginning
of an invasion ?
Does it happen in all cemeteries ?
Or is Buffalora just an exception ?
Who knows ?
And in the end , who cares ?
I 'm just doing my job !
Good morning , Engineer !
How are you doing today ?
Fine , Miss Chiaromondo .
And you ?
The cemetery is open , isn 't it ?
For you , anytime .
Oh , hello , cutie !
Here .
How are you ?
He 's happy .
He likes it when the sun shines .
I 'm not an engineer !
And you 're no cutie !
Hmm .
Poor Gnaghi !
On his ID card it reads , " Distinctive visible marks : All " .
He has a real passion for dead leaves .
He can 't stand it when the wind blows them away .
Oh , well .
We all do what we can not to think about life .
The most beautiful living woman I have ever seen !
Will I see her again ?
I just came to water the flowers
on your poor father 's grave .
Husband .
How long has he been dead ?
Two weeks .
Thank goodness .
What ?
I mean , I 'm very sorry .
Have you no respect for pain ?
I know how these things are .
You 'll see .
In time , pain heals .
It 's not healing a bit !
He was wonderful !
He was a wonderful lover .
Incredible , tireless .
He was fantastic !
Hmmm .
Mmm .
I messed it all up .
I 've lost her .
Will I see her again ?
Hey , Franco !
Woo-hoo .
Franco is the only living person who even calls me .
Now and then I stop by his office
to remind myself what he looks like .
You can 't live on memories alone .
It 's for you .
Sign as usual .
You got a pen ?
- No . - Hold on a sec .
Here we are .
Did you have any visits last night ?
A couple , yeah .
All this extra work .
It 's much if they pay me any more !
Tell the mayor .
Oh tell the man and then what ?
They 'll close the cemetery .
Goodbye job and goodbye house .
Come on , who do think would believe you ?
Listen .
I don 't care if you don 't believe me , Franco .
You 're not the one who pays me .
I believe you .
Believe you .
And you 're right .
At least have him pay you the overtime .
Good !
Well , let 's go to the mayor , then .
It 's not that easy .
Oh .
First you have to fill out an M3 form .
Report with an M3 form , forms .
I can speed things up a bit for you .
It 's easier just to shoot them .
One M3 form .
Hello , hello , hello .
Going to get our willies wet tonight ?
Some of us , yeah .
Hell , at a certain point in life ,
you realize you know more dead people than living .
Sorry about the other day , I was a bit crass .
I didn 't mean to be .
My name 's Francesco Dellamorte .
You know , this is the only job I could get ,
even with a degree in biology !
Anyway , we all end up here
sooner or later , don 't we ?
I got a great little house .
Want to see it ?
I don 't live alone , I 've got a helper , Gnaghi .
He 's a real conversationalist .
The cemetery 's small but it has got a marvelous ossuary .
An ossuary !
I have never seen anything so exciting !
Neither have I.
It 's like in my dreams !
This is my dream .
I couldn 't ask for anything more !
Me neither .
You know , you 've got a real nice ossuary .
Thanks .
You will allow me to return , won 't you ?
You will allow me to kiss you just once , won 't you ?
No , Not like this .
Like this .
No !
I must be faithful to the memory of my husband !
I can 't !
I can 't .
It 's not my fault .
It 's this place .
I feel strange tremors .
It 's not the cold , I 'm not afraid .
This place wants me to , It 's forcing me to ...
I don 't want to !
I can 't !
I can 't .
No !
Don 't be afraid .
It 's just ignis fatuus .
Why here ?
Why on your poor husband 's grave ?
I 've never kept anything from him .
We trusted each other implicitly .
He would have liked to know .
Well , if that 's the case ...
These lights !
Let them watch .
What 's better than watching two lovers making love ?
Just to have a bit of privacy .
Sorry , the lady wants stars only .
It 's never been like this before ,
with anybody but you .
No-one will ever make us part .
Gnaghi , the gun !
I can explain , listen to me !
You have always been so understanding !
That 's life .
It 's nothing , my love .
You 're fine .
Great !
Just when I don 't need it any more !
Nyah .
Well , don 't just stand there , go call Dr. Vercesi !
Go on , get the doctor !
Go on , move !
Nothing will separate us .
I swear .
Nothing !
Nothing will separate us .
Nothing , my love .
Nothing !
Not even death .
Dellamorte ?
Are you in there ?
Dellamorte !
Oh , Jesus , you scared me to death !
You 're looking for me , Chief Straniero ?
Yes .
Dr. Vercesi called .
What happened last night ?
Well you know .
Why are you asking me ?
She 's dead .
I know she 's dead .
But how did that happen ?
Her husband .
Oh sure !
He came back from the dead .
He raped and bit her to death .
Is that what he did ?
No , he didn 't rape her .
Oh , you always crack me up , you know ?
Oh Dr. Vercesi , are you spying on us ?
No !
I 've drawn up the death certificate .
Her heart stopped from fear .
It wasn 't a bite that killed her .
She died while making , well you know , doing it .
Ah .
You know what that means , my boy ?
I 'll have to look somewhere else
for the creep who killed her .
You are no longer a suspect .
Why not ?
Well , you know what I mean .
Look !
Don 't make me say it .
Go on , you can say it .
I don 't mind .
I 'm impotent !
Don 't use that word .
A young man like you , at your age !
Did she have any relatives ?
Nope .
No relatives , no friends .
Well , I have to say that ...
Shit !
This is definitely not my style .
Can I keep her here ?
If you pay for the funeral of course ,
You can do whatever the hell you want with her .
Does that wrap it up then ?
Yeah , except for a killer running loose .
Care to join me for a cup of tea .
Ah , the weather 's changing at last !
I can 't forgive myself for having lied to you .
I don 't have a degree in biology .
Never even finished high school .
I haven 't read more than two books in my whole life .
One , never finished ,
and the other 's the phone book .
I don 't want her to become a Returner .
I don 't want to see her again .
No !
Yes , my love .
Don 't make me do it !
But you do it so well , so well .
Not to you .
It will be better with me than with the others .
Nyah !
You do it !
Well go on !
If you finish fast , I 'll buy you an ice cream .
Nyah .
Here comes the Unforgiven !
The man whose micro-dick 's so small he pees with tweezers !
Tweezers ?
That 's a good one . - Way to go !
He could become a woman .
That would solve it !
What is it that you hear about them sewing them back on ?
Yeah , they can stitch them right on ,
if of course you don 't have one to start with .
Forget it , I started that rumor .
The more they laugh , the further away they seem .
You can never be too different , Gnaghi .
Maybe you can .
Engineer !
Engineer , Engineer !
Come , have a seat .
Well , well , well .
What a surprise .
Yes , it 's a miracle seeing you here .
It 's a miracle seeing you here , Mr. Mayor .
So , how are things , down at our cemetery ?
How are things ?
Well , how do you think things are ?
Population 's shrinking isn 't it ?
By leaps and bounds .
Hey , you 're lucky , my dear engineer .
You just can 't imagine how things are at the town hall .
Now that the elections are upon us .
It is chaos !
Right , Inspector ? - Yeah , it 's a free for all .
Nobody wants to lose their job !
According to a new deal -
Daddy , what 's this ?
This is my assistant , Gnaghi .
He 's sweet !
Will you buy him , Daddy ?
That 's great !
It even knows how to cry .
Gnaghi , don 't sit so close to her .
Could you move over , darling ?
Would you tell your daughter to move over , please ?
Oh yes , of course .
Sometimes Gnaghi gets a bit excited .
Oh , I 'm sure .
He 's charming .
Now where was I ?
Oh , yes , just the same .
- I see . - Precisely .
By keeping things the same we can change more effectively .
What 's it doing ?
Dancing ?
No , no , he 's about to -
What the hell are you doing , Valentina ?
He threw up on me , Claudio !
Oh , new fan .
Would you like to go for a ride ?
I knew you 'd understand .
Take off !
By the way , one of these days
I have to talk to you about the cemetery .
The youth of today !
They 're so emotional !
Come on , Gnaghi , get in , for God 's sake !
Don 't do this .
Just get in the car !
It 's not the end of the world .
It didn 't even bother her !
She understood it was just
a demonstration of your affection .
Anyway , it 's not the first time you threw up
over a woman , is it ?
Nyah !
Come on , Gnaghi , get in !
Look , first love doesn 't count .
It 's last love that counts .
Oh .
Nobody came today .
I was a bit bored .
Not even the admiral .
He 's just disappeared !
Let 's hope tomorrow .
Come again and stay awhile .
Oh , he was such a distinguished looking man !
The Admiral , always used to bring me , always a touch of Sambuca !
Oh , come on , Gnaghi !
You 'll get over it , you 'll see .
Time passes , nothing seems the same .
It just gets worse !
God , is it ever difficult trying to make you feel better !
What were you doing with the Mayor 's daughter anyway ?
She 's only a child !
Nyah !
Oh yeah !
That is not true .
You 're not a child , Gnaghi .
You 're a year older than I am .
Anyway , one day you 'll settle down
with some poor creature like yourself .
Meanwhile , what do you care ?
They all end up here sooner or later , Gnaghi .
Often sooner than later .
Whoo-hoo , faster !
Open it up !
If Daddy could see us now !
He 'd kill me .
Claudio !
Off we go ! - Go !
Go , go !
Go !
Yay !
- Hang on ! - Eat our dust !
Four motorcycles racing .
The Mayor 's daughter was on one of them .
Her head was sliced right off
had to sew it back on the body .
The bikes crashed into a bus loaded with scouts
on their way back from a church sponsored outing .
Slaughter of the innocents !
And they were all so young .
Right !
They thought their life was ahead of them ,
but in fact it had already passed them by !
Well , you 've got your hands full .
Oh !
More than you know .
Gnaghi , we 're going to need a lot of bullets .
? Now I do my scouting in a marble tomb ?
? Never should 've gone out on the Boy Scout picnic ?
? Never should 've never should 've gone just then ?
? Never should 've ?
? Now I 'll never go again ?
Oh , Claudio !
Take me with you !
Don 't leave me all alone !
Claudio !
Take me with you , my love !
Oh , no sweetheart ,
my son wasn 't with you !
He was promised to the Mayor 's daughter !
But he loved me !
- Liar ! - He was mine .
He loved me , only me !
Have you no respect for a mother ?
We 're born to die .
Born merely to die !
Do you remember ?
Just yesterday , she was alive , happy .
Dear Gnaghi even threw up on her and she took it so well !
And now , she 's gone .
And right on the eve of the elections !
I 'd better get the pickax and shovel .
Pumpkin , how could you do this to me ?
Is it true what they say ,
that the dead come back to life here at night ?
Tell me !
Okay !
Who told you that ?
Is it true or not ?
Shhh .
What if it is ?
I 've got to see Claudio again !
I have to know whether he loved me or her .
If I hear anything , I 'll let you know .
No , wait !
Go away !
I haven 't got time for the living .
Gnaghi ?
Gnaghi !
Gnaghi , they came back sooner than we thought !
Gnaghi , wake up !
Gnaghi , watch out !
Oh , Gnaghi , I 'm sorry !
I didn 't mean to .
Right !
That 's it .
Time 's up and ,
I want you upstairs , and ready in five minutes , okay ?
Oh , no !
What 's she doing here ?
Hey !
Visiting hours are over !
No !
You 're gonna take me away from him !
Quick !
Get the fuck over here , quick !
No !
Claudio !
No , Claudio !
Take me with you !
Darn !
Stupid cow !
Come on !
Please , wait !
Claudio , please , take me with you !
Tell me you only love me !
Please !
Claudio ?
You only love me , right ?
Hey .
Damn !
Always shoots to the right when it 's cold .
Gnaghi !
No , please don 't !
He 's only eating me !
Move aside .
Mind your own business .
I can be eaten by whoever I please !
This is my business .
They pay me for it .
The living dead and the dying living are all the same .
Cut from the same cloth .
But disposing of dead people is a public service .
Whereas you 're in all sorts of trouble
if you kill someone when they 're still alive .
Wait !
This way they 'll be together forever .
I 'm sentimental !
Patience , Gnaghi .
In love , it 's the waiting that 's the best part .
You have to learn how to wait .
What 's your name again ?
Gna .
Gnaghi .
I 'm Valentina .
Haven 't I seen you before ?
Mm-hmm .
Oh , yeah .
Now I remember .
You threw up on me .
How sweet !
But I like shy boys .
And you never say no to a kiss .
Take advantage .
I 'm certainly in no position to refuse .
Besides , I don 't think I 'd refuse anyway .
Hmm ?
False alarm !
It was only a cat .
No use you trying to help me , little thing !
If I can 't do it , imagine you !
Putting this skull together
is one of the most difficult things in the world .
You know , you really are disgusting when you eat , Gnaghi !
Nyah .
Yes , you 're right .
I suppose it all does get mixed up
in the stomach in the end .
What is it ?
That wasn 't a cat .
We can 't !
I 'm alive .
And you 're dead .
I 'm not prejudiced , my love .
I killed her .
Nyah .
I killed her !
I killed her .
The first time , when her husband bit her ,
she wasn 't really dead .
When she woke up , and I shot her , she was alive .
I killed her .
I killed the only woman I ever loved .
I shot her with my eyes closed , didn 't aim for the head .
That 's why she came back .
God , what an idiot !
Now am I infected , too ?
Will I be a Returner when I die ?
Who knows if Gnaghi ,
no , poor Gnaghi !
He 'd never have the guts to crush my skull with a shovel .
Hey .
I 'm not dead , you idiot !
A bite can 't kill you !
Nyah .
Good morning , Engineer !
Miss Chiaromondo , I 'm not an engineer .
Are you or are you not the watchman of this cemetery ?
Well , of course I am .
You are therefore an engineer .
By the way ,
which of these do you think would be better on my tombstone ?
Both .
I like the opinion of a handsome young man !
Goodbye , Engineer !
Good morning , cutie !
But that 's the phone book !
Are you crazy ?
That is my favorite reading !
Nyah .
Just because we 've got the new ones ,
it doesn 't mean to say we have to throw the old ones away .
These books are classics !
Gnaghi !
Gna !
Stop killing the dead .
They 're mine .
If you don 't want the dead coming back to life ,
why don 't you just kill the living , shoot them in the head ?
Are you listening to me ?
Hello ?
Greetings from alternative Town Hall .
- Franco , how are you ? - Bored .
Am I disturbing you ?
No , you never disturb me .
Just called to talk about the scandal .
- Gnaghi , the door ! - All that crap .
What did you say ?
What the hell was that ?
Nothing , I 'm just working .
- What ? - Oh you know , daily grind .
Nothing but the daily grind .
You 're telling me .
Sometimes I feel like shooting myself .
Nyah !
How 's everything in your life ?
How are dear Mara and Cinzia ?
You know , I sometimes wonder if they actually exist , Franco .
I mean , you do have a wife and daughter , don 't you ?
I only ask ' cause ,
sometimes think I made it all up .
Franco , you do make me laugh .
You 'll get out one day .
Buffalora will be nothing but a bad , bad memory .
Yeah , or maybe not .
If only I could get unstuck .
I feel like a fly on fly paper .
Mmm .
Oh well , you 'll see , Franco .
Mara is going to get tired of you .
And Cinzia will grow up to hate you .
Then you 'll be free !
Free to see what the rest of the world looks like .
What do you think the rest
of the world looks like ?
The rest of the world ?
Mm-hmm .
Mmm .
Who knows if the rest of the world even exists !
Look who it is !
At times I get ahead of my work .
Work !
Dellamorte !
Gnaghi !
Francesco Dellamorte .
Mmm .
Where were you between 11 and 12 : 30 last night ?
In bed .
Any witnesses ?
I was talking to my friend Franco on the telephone
and I fell asleep .
Why ?
What happened ?
Some fucking maniac killed seven people in town .
More work ?
Well , you 're gonna go to jail
unless you have an alibi .
Why me ?
Because your car was seen driving
around the streets last night , that 's why .
That 's impossible .
No one can drive that wreck apart from me .
Actually , I don 't think it was you .
I think it was your assistant .
Gnaghi can 't even roller-skate .
Neither can I , so what ?
I want to question him immediately .
God , the weather 's gone bad .
Please , Let me talk to him first .
Just have him come right out , will you ?
Don 't you ever clean that place ?
Jesus Christ , it stinks !
? When all is sad , when you 're alone , it feels so bad ?
? And waits again for love to start ?
? To feel the beating of the heart ?
Mmmm .
Gnaghi !
Gnaghi , I had a terrible dream last night .
I dreamt I went out and killed seven real people .
Hi !
Remember me ?
Dellamorte !
You 've got important visitors !
? There comes a time when death is sad ?
? When you 're all alone , it feels so bad ?
You 'll understand , Engineer ,
after this massacre the voters
are furious with me .
They 've been voting for you for 15 years .
And if we don 't find this maniac , Straniero ,
there won 't be a 16th !
What 's your daughter got to do with it ?
Now that the whole town is in mourning .
I want to show them I 'm grieving as well .
I 'll have some pictures taken of the body
and put a blow-up on my election posters .
And underneath something like ,
" If you 've had a death in the family ,
vote for someone who suffers like you " .
What do you think ?
Well , you know , it 's a thought !
Or " Vote for a man who has lost all other happiness " .
Ready to shoot ?
So what do I do ?
Take one from the neck down ?
Engineer !
What 's the meaning of this ?
Daddy !
Daddykin !
Did you hear that ?
I don 't know .
It depends . - Daddypie !
Daddypoo !
Valentina !
Pumpkin !
The plot thickens !
Pumpkin , where are you ?
Where are you ?
Your Daddy 's here !
Oh where are you ?
Stop blubbering and come on in !
Oh .
Coming .
Here I am , little one !
Mmmm .
Jeez , it stinks in here .
It 's my fault , Daddy .
Oh , my God !
Valentina !
What are you doing on TV ?
I 'm rotting fast , Daddy .
Nyah .
You , you stuttering monster !
You 're the one who hurt my little girl !
No , daddy !
He loves me !
Step aside .
I command you , as your mayor !
With your consent , I 'd like to marry Gnaghi .
This horrible thing ?
Nyah .
I 'm not such a great catch either , Daddy .
Not as long dear , as I 've got a breath in my body .
All right .
We 'll fix that right away .
Help me , Engineer !
I 'm not an engineer .
I 'm sorry Gnaghi .
She was really beginning to , go off a bit there , wasn 't she ?
He 's dead ?
He 's dead .
Who took a bite out of his neck ?
Oh not me or Gnaghi .
Take a mold of our teeth .
You 'll see they won 't match .
Then who did it ?
Well relax Straniero ,
this won 't be your first unsolved case , will it ?
Hold it !
Come on , Gnaghi .
The world 's full of girls like that .
And they 've got bodies , too !
By the way , do you know what my mother 's maiden name was ?
Huh ?
You 'd never believe it if I told you .
She was called Dellamore .
Dellamore .
That means " Love " .
You 're not the only person in the world
who 's lost a lover , Gnaghi .
Hey !
Get down !
What are you doing ?
Get down from there .
Forget it , Engineer .
Go home .
You 're supposed to be setting a good example .
Now will you get back to your coffin immediately !
You can 't stop me .
You owe your job to me .
Remember ?
Get down or I 'll shoot .
You can 't .
I 'm the mayor !
Ex .
Mister Dellamorte ?
What ?
I 'm Civardi , the new mayor .
Why the barbed wire ?
Do they climb in at night ?
No .
They climb out , sometimes .
Would you mind coming down ?
You reported an epidemic which affects the dead .
You claim they come to life within seven days of burial .
It says so , right here .
An M3 report .
- Didn 't you fill it out ? - No .
Oh , splendid !
So you 'll provide us with a denial .
Just sign here .
Franco must have sent it .
What a nice thought !
Nothing happened .
Nothing ever happens .
If the press got hold of something like this ,
not only will Buffalora be a laughing stock ,
but you 'd lose your job .
My personal secretary .
Mr. Dellamorte .
A pleasure , a real pleasure , Mr. Dellamorte .
Thank you .
You and I are going to get along just fine .
Goodbye .
Your name .
I didn 't get your name !
Will I see her again ?
Hi !
God !
I 'm , I 'm sorry .
I didn 't mean to frighten you , it 's just ,
I was expecting someone else .
Miss !
Ever since I got to Buffalora ,
strange things have been happening to me .
It 's as if I 've been here before .
And that grave , and you , Mr. Dellamorte ,
it 's as if I 've known you forever ,
as if I 've loved you forever !
You love me too ?
Why ?
Who else is there ?
I love you as well .
I love you , I love you !
I 've heard what they say about you in town .
Is it true that you ,
I mean , you , you can 't ...
No , no , no , you don 't want to believe town gossip .
Because I can only love an impotent man .
Yeah , it 's true , it 's true .
I like men ,
but their manhood terrifies me ,
I can 't stand the thought of them having a ,
I mean , you understand .
It 's a sort of phobia I have .
I don 't have one I ,
I don 't have anything at all .
Will you marry me ?
Mmmm .
I 'm getting married .
Nyah !
I 'm really getting married .
Don 't pretend you didn 't hear everything .
Nyah !
Oh yeah ?
Why not then ?
Go ahead , expect , ah !
Goodness gracious !
What are you saying ? - You heard me .
My dear boy , you must be very run down .
I 'm gonna give you some pills .
Dr. Vercesi , I 'm serious .
Look , I 'm not going to be intimidated in my own surgery .
That waiting room there is full of people
with good honest diseases .
I 'll pay you .
Yes , I know , but ,
how can I ?
I mean , everybody knows that
you haven 't got one .
I see you , you have got one .
Well , when would you like me to relieve you
of your problem ?
Now .
What are you waiting for ?
Get on with it !
Now what ?
I told you .
I don 't want an anesthetic .
- It 's not an anesthetic . - What is it , then ?
One shot of this , it 'll be almost
as if you 've never had one .
It lasts for over a month .
Look , please , don 't make me cut it off .
Today I 'm just not up to it .
What are you doing ?
Turning over ?
I have to give you the shot in the front .
Front where ?
Hold still , I 'll just make a puncture .
That fucking butcher !
Must 've given me some kind of infection .
Gnaghi , I 'm hovering between life and death !
Nyah !
Yeah , you 're right .
I suppose I 'm used to this condition .
If that 's her , don 't let her in .
Tell her I 'm not here .
I don 't want her to see me like this .
- I must see Mr. Dellamorte . - Nyah !
Please .
I 've got to speak to him .
Is he in there ? - Nyah !
I 'd give my life to be dead !
Gnaghi , it doesn 't hurt anymore !
I think I 'm better .
Nyah .
When did that happen ?
She was our nicest client .
The best always die first !
Nyah .
Where have you been ?
I though I 'd go mad .
If you only knew what happened to me !
I must talk to you .
We 'll always be together .
Yes , my love , yes .
I don 't know how to say this ,
but the mayor raped me .
- No ! - Wait !
I liked it .
Not the violence , no .
But after that we did it again nicely .
So that I 'd forgive him
and it was wonderful !
Do you understand ?
This means I 'm cured .
I don 't have a phobia anymore .
I can 't marry you now .
I 'm going to marry him .
That doesn 't mean anything , though .
I mean , nothing 's changed between us .
I still love you .
You know that .
I just love you in a different way .
But you 're important to me .
He knows .
I mean , about you and me .
He 's a wonderful man .
He said he 's happy we can be friends .
We can still see each other .
Nothing 's changed .
Everything 's just as it was .
Everything !
You look for Death
in the clear night .
You tell her you still love her .
That you are her slave ,
that she 's still your queen .
Death , Death , Death , the whore .
No , I 'd only do it for the fear .
I 'd come back just to experience the same fear again ,
to be afraid , always to be afraid .
Hi !
Is that white VW outside yours ?
We 're on foot .
Could you give us a lift ?
It 's not very far .
Go on !
I 'm Magda .
And this is Laura .
How far is it ?
This is where we live .
With another girlfriend .
Do you want to come up for a drink ?
Oh come on .
You 're not afraid of two college girls , are you ?
Make a wish .
I grant wishes .
I want you to fall in love with me .
But I 'm already in love with you .
Haven 't you noticed ?
It 's cold in here !
If you 'd like to wash , there 's a sink there .
I didn 't mean your face , silly !
I don 't know whether I can do it .
I 've been taking some medication .
I don 't think your medication is working .
Do you love me ?
Yes , if you stay all night .
All my life , too .
Come on !
Let 's rest a bit .
Why ?
You 've come three times already .
Twice .
The third one was faked .
Oh .
Shhh .
She 's sleeping , she 's been studying all day ,
she 's got an exam tomorrow .
I just wanted , I just wanted to get some wine .
Sit down .
I 'll get you some .
Did Laura tell you you can pay me ?
Pay you ?
School 's expensive , my friend .
I have to pay you ?
We don 't have a scholarship , you know ?
Besides , it 's only 100,000 lira .
She told me she loved me .
That 's 150 .
She wants me to stay the night .
200 .
Is a check all right ?
It 's money , isn 't it ?
Hurry , darling .
I 'm cold .
Come and warm me up .
I need your warmth .
Warm me up .
Coming , love .
Now you 'll be warm forever .
Mmm .
This time I 'm really through with love .
I bet you 'd like to know where I was between one
and three last night , wouldn 't you ?
Oh , I know , I know .
Here we are .
Have no fear .
I won 't tell anybody about this check .
She is the reason I came here .
We 're both worldly men , aren 't we ?
But this could be proof against -
Proof against whom ?
We 've already arrested the guilty party .
After setting fire to the apartment ,
he went home , killed his wife and daughter ,
then turned himself in .
He 's at the hospital , the psychiatric ward .
Somebody 's stolen my crimes !
Sir ?
Excuse me .
This section 's closed to the public .
I 've come to see the killer .
But you can 't go in there .
He 's in a coma .
He drank a whole bottle of iodine .
I have to take his measurements .
Franco !
You looked a lot better
than the last time we talked on the phone .
Thief !
You 're a thief !
You may have killed your wife and daughter ,
I 'll give you that .
But it was me who knocked off the three girls !
What are you doing , stealing my murders ?
What kind of fucking friend do you think you are ?
I suppose you thought you were doing me a favor .
Put that out immediately .
Smoking is not allowed in here !
Shut up .
He 's in a coma , he doesn 't even notice .
Shit !
What did you say ?
Everything 's shit .
The only thing that 's not shitty is sleep .
What are you doing on the floor , sister ?
She 's praying .
Friend of yours ?
Mmm .
Look , he hasn 't got any relatives ,
and the coma he 's in is irreversible .
Give me a signature and I 'll pull the plug now .
Fuck off !
Here you go , put it back in there .
I won 't let you die , until you give me an explanation .
Why did you steal my murders ?
Don 't you think anything I do counts ?
Oh , my God !
What happened ?
They killed each other .
It was a settling of scores .
Don 't you believe me ?
- No ! - Tough !
No , no !
Sorry about that .
So , don 't you have anything to say to your only friend ?
Who are you ?
I don 't know you .
I don 't know who you are .
Go away !
Dellamorte , wait !
For God 's sake , wait !
There 's another maniac on the loose .
He 's on the fourth floor killing people .
He already shot three .
You 've got a gun .
That 's good .
Now you can defend yourself .
Hey !
Take my advice and get the hell out of here , quick !
Straniero !
It was me !
You and I are both the same .
We kill out of indifference .
Out of love , sometimes .
But never out of hate .
Now I don 't know who 's dead or alive .
I 'm sick of killing .
So I 'm leaving the game , brother .
Dellamorte Dellamore bids you farewell
and he 's on his way .
Where to ?
Better get out of here .
Even the statues are talking .
Where do you think you 're going ,
if you haven 't yet understood the difference
between life and me ?
Gnaghi , you 're not bringing that .
Nyah !
That coffin is not coming with us .
Yeah , I missed that one .
Don 't worry , I 'll get the next one .
Nyah !
Oh calm down , I know every bump on this road !
There 's one .
Look !
I 've never been this far .
We made it , Gnaghi !
Who could 've imagined this ?
Wider than all the streets of Buffalora put together .
It never seems to end .
Nyah .
Hang on , Gnaghi .
Past this tunnel is the rest of the world !
What do you think the rest of the world looks like , Gnaghi ?
Can you imagine ?
You 're right .
It 's beyond imagination .
I should have known it .
The rest of the world doesn 't exist !
Gnaghi !
Gnaghi , you weren 't hit that hard , come on !
I 'll take you to the car .
Come on !
Gnaghi !
Why are you going on like this ?
You just got cut , come on , man !
Get up , I 'll take you to the car .
Come on , man !
Get up .
What ?
Gnaghi !
Don 't leave me alone , now !
Oh , God !
Death , Death , Death comes sweeping down .
Filthy Death , the leering clown ,
Death on wings , Death by surprise .
Veiling evil from worldly eyes .
Death that 's born as Life succumbs ,
while Death and Love , two kindred drums ,
beat the time till Judgment Day .
An actor in a passion play ,
without beginning , without end .
Evermore , amen .
You were my best friend .
I didn 't even realize it .
Could you take me home , please ?
Nyah !